Magic in the Moonlight is a comedy, drama, romance film directed by Woody Allen.
Set in the 1920s French Riviera, a master magician is
commissioned to try and expose a psychic as a fraud.
Stanley Crawford, played by Colin Firth.
Sophie Baker, played by Emma Stone.
Brice, played by Hamish Linklater.
Mrs. Baker, played by Marcia Gay Harden.
Grace, played by Jacki Weaver.
Caroline, played by Erica Leerhsen.
Magic in the Moonlight is a 2014 romantic comedy film
written and directed by Woody Allen.
The film stars Eileen Atkins, Colin Firth, Marcia Gay Harden, Hamish
Linklater, Emma Stone, Simon McBurney, and Jacki Weaver.
Set in the 1920s on the French Riviera, the film was released in the
United States on July 25, 2014, by Sony Pictures Classics.
Magic in the Moonlight received a mixed reception.
Critics praised the performances of Firth and Stone,
but found the film's writing formulaic.
The film explores themes of magic, provence, aunt, spiritualist.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.